University of Connecticut, Board of Trustees Records 1987.0007
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
University of Connecticut, Board of Trustees Records
undated, 1881-
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1987.0007
96 Linear Feet
In April 1881, the Connecticut General Assembly established the Storrs Agricultural School after accepting a gift of 170 acres of land, several frame buildings, and money from Charles and Augustus Storrs. The School opened on September 28, 1881, with twelve students in the first class. Before the turn of the century there were two name changes (Storrs Agricultural College 1893, Connecticut Agricultural College 1899). In 1933, two years after the institution celebrated its fiftieth anniversary, it became Connecticut State College, a name more in keeping with its steady advances and broadened mission. Six years later, in 1939, the General Assembly designated the institution the University of Connecticut, an acknowledgment of the institution's developing importance to the State in graduate and professional education, research and public service.
History
In April 1881, the Connecticut General Assembly established the Storrs Agricultural School after accepting a gift of 170 acres of land, several frame buildings, and money from Charles and Augustus Storrs. The School opened on 28 September 1881, with twelve students in the first class. Before the turn of the century there were two name changes (Storrs Agricultural College 1893, Connecticut Agricultural College 1899). In 1933, two years after the institution celebrated its fiftieth anniversary, it became Connecticut State College, a name more in keeping with its steady advances and broadened mission. Six years later, in 1939, the General Assembly designated the institution the University of Connecticut, an acknowledgment of the institution's developing importance to the State in graduate and professional education, research and public service.
The University of Connecticut is recognized as the state's flagship institution of higher learning. Since its establishment, the University has grown to include 13 Schools and Colleges at its main campus in Storrs, separate Schools of Law and Social Work in Hartford, five regional campuses throughout the state and Schools of Medicine and Dentistry at the UConn Health Center in Farmington.
UConn is a Land Grant and Sea Grant College and a Space Grant Consortium institution. The University spans 4,104 acres at its main campus and five regional campuses, and an additional 162 acres at the UConn Health Center in Farmington.
Designated a Carnegie Foundation Research University-Extensive, UConn has more than 70 focused research centers where faculty, graduate students and undergraduates explore everything from improving human health to enhancing public education and protecting the country's natural resources.
The Board of Trustees is comprised of 19 members: 12 appointed by the Governor; two elected by alumni; two elected by students; and three ex-officio, including the Governor and the Commissioners of Agriculture and Education. Additional information on the Board is available on its official website.
Scope and Content
The collection contains the official minutes, reports, recommendations and resolutions of the Board of Trustees of the University of Connecticut, as well as its subcommittees and task forces. The records date from the founding of the institution in 1881 as the Storrs Agricultural School through the present.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in the following series:
Series I: Minutes (1881- ) contains agendas, official minutes and supporting documentation and attachments.
Series II: Correspondence and Supporting materials (1970-1992) includes materials made available to the Board to assist in the decision making process and correspondence to and from Board members.
Series III: Subject Files (undated, 1970-1985) contains alphabetically arranged files and documents related to the Board on a wide variety of subjects.
Series IV: Committee Files (undated, 1977-2011) includes Budget and Finance, Buildings, Grounds and Environments, Health Affairs and Institutional Policy Committees.
Series V: Biographies and Plans (undated, 1936-1972>) consists of Trustee biographies, statements, plans and studies of the board. Biographies are arranged alphabetically while the remaining material is arranged chronologically.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Board of trustees meeting, 1995: Feb. 10, Dodd Video 263
Acquisition Information
The records are transferred to Archives & Special Collections by the University President's Office for permanent retention.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Bibliography
Stemmons, Walter. Connecticut Agricultural College: A History.
Publications (documents); Correspondence; Financial Records; Connecticut (state); Administrative records; History; Education, Higher; Universities and colleges; University of Connecticut. Board of Trustees; University of Connecticut
- Series I: Minutes, 1881-
  Location of Copies or Alternate Formats
  Board of Trustees meeting Agenda (2003-present), Attachments (2008-present) and Minutes 1903-present are available electronically in the UConn DigitalCommons.
  - 1881 April 26 - 1902 December 29 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - 1889 May 9 - 1896 December 30 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - pp. 1 - 4, 1901 July 11 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - pp. 5 - 31, 1901 September 13 - 1902 July 16 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - pp. 32 - 54, 1902 October 18 - 1903 August 4 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - pp. 55 - 73, 1903 November 7 - 1904 August 4 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - pp. 74 - 91, 1904 November 28 - 1905 August 3 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - pp. 92 - 114, 1905 October 24 - 1906 July 26 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - pp. 115 - 137, 1906 September 28 - 1907 July 30 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - pp. 138 - 156, 1907 October 17 - 1908 August 19 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - pp. 157 - 169, 1908 September 1 - 1909 August 6 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - pp. 170 - 189, 1909 October 1 - 1910 July 26 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - pp. 190 - 208, 1910 September 12 - 1911 August 8 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - pp. 209 - 230, 1911 September 26 - 1912 August 15 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - pp. 231 - 257, 1912 September 12 - 1913 August 26 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - pp. 258 - 280, 1913 October 14 - 1914 August 18 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - pp. 281 - 318, 1914 September 1 - 1915 July 21 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - pp. 319 - 393, 1915 October 20 - 1916 August 16 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - pp. 394 - 445, 1916 September 20 - 1917 August 14 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - pp. 446 - 473, 1 - 46, 1917 September 27 - 1918 July 30 (Box 2:, Folder 20)
  - pp. 47 - 131, 1918 September 10 - 1919 August 12 (Box 2:, Folder 21)
  - pp. 132 - 194, 1919 September 10 - 1920 August 18 (Box 2:, Folder 22)
  - pp. 195 - 222, 1920 September 7 - 1921 August 3 (Box 2:, Folder 23)
  - pp. 223 - 274, 1921 September 21 - 1922 August 19 (Box 2:, Folder 24)
  - pp.275 - 318, 1922 September 21 - 1923 July 19 (Box 2:, Folder 25)
  - pp. 319 - 360, 1923 September 19 - 1924 August 6 (Box 2:, Folder 26)
  - pp. 361 - 398, 1924 October 15 - 1925 August 19 (Box 2:, Folder 27)
  - pp. 399 - 441, 1925 October 21 - 1926 July 21 (Box 2:, Folder 28)
  - pp. 442 - 492, 1926 September 15 - 1927 August 5 (Box 2:, Folder 29)
  - pp. 493 - 568, 1927 September 14 - 1928 August 22 (Box 2:, Folder 30)
  - pp. 569 - 644, 1928 September 19 - 1929 July 17 (Box 2:, Folder 31)
  - pp. 645 - 689, 1929 September 11 - 1930 August 27 (Box 2:, Folder 32)
  - pp. 690 - 734, 1930 September 10 - 1931 August 5 (Box 2:, Folder 33)
  - pp. 735 - 765, 1931 September 9 - 1932 July 19 (Box 2:, Folder 34)
  - pp. 766 - 799, 1932 September 12 - 1933 June 30 (Box 2:, Folder 35)
  - pp. 800 - 841, 1933 September 20 - 1934 August 10 (Box 2:, Folder 36)
  - pp. 842 - 878, 1934 September 19 - 1935 July 31 (Box 3:, Folder 37)
  - pp. 879 - 913, 1935 September 4 - 1936 August 18 (Box 3:, Folder 38)
  - pp. 914 - 931, 1936 September 16 - 1937 August 25 (Box 3:, Folder 39)
  - pp. 932 - 944, 1937 September 22 - 1938 June 22 (Box 3:, Folder 40)
  - pp. 945 - 961, 1938 September 28 - 1939 July 5 (Box 3:, Folder 41)
  - pp. 962 - 1000, 1939 September 20 - 1940 July 10 (Box 3:, Folder 42)
  - pp. 1001 - 1043, 1940 October 2 - 1941 July 9 (Box 3:, Folder 43)
  - pp. 1046 - 1102, 1941 September 24 - 1942 July 15 (Box 3:, Folder 44)
  - pp. 1103 - 1155, 1942 September 1 - 1943 July 27 (Box 3:, Folder 45)
  - pp. 1156 - 1251, 1943 September 15 - 1944 August 30 (Box 3:, Folder 46)
  - pp. 1252 - 1320, 1944 September 20 - 1945 July 18 (Box 3:, Folder 47)
  - pp. 1321 - 1396, 1945 September 19 - 1946 July 17 (Box 3:, Folder 48)
  - pp. 1397 - 1486, 1946 September 19 - 1947 July 17 (Box 3:, Folder 49)
  - pp. 1487 - 1553, 1947 October 15 - 1947 December 17 (Box 3:, Folder 50)
  - pp. 1554 - 1650, 1948 February 4 - 1948 July 21 (Box 3:, Folder 51)
  - pp. 1651 - 1692, 1948 October 20 - 1949 June 20 (Box 3:, Folder 52)
  - pp. 1693 - 1752, 1949 September 21 - 1950 July 19 (Box 3:, Folder 53)
  - pp. 1753 - 1832, 1950 September 27 - 1951 May 16 (Box 3:, Folder 54)
  - pp. 1833 - 1885, 1951 September 19 - 1951 November 2 (Box 3:, Folder 55)
  - pp. 1886 - 1964, 1952 January 16 - 1952 July 30 (Box 3:, Folder 56)
  - pp. 1964 - 2024, 1952 September 17 - 1952 November 19 (Box 4:, Folder 57)
  - pp. 2025 - 2092, 1953 January 26 - 1953 July 27 (Box 4:, Folder 58)
  - pp. 2093 - 2127, 1953 September 16 - 1953 November 18 (Box 4:, Folder 59)
  - pp. 2128 - 2170, 1954 January 20 - 1954 February 19 (Box 4:, Folder 60)
  - pp. 2170 - 2223, 1954 April 23 - 1954 August 25 (Box 4:, Folder 61)
  - pp. 2224 - 2253, 1954 September 22 - 1954 November 24 (Box 4:, Folder 62)
  - pp. 2254 - 2316, 1955 February 2 - 1955 July 20 (Box 4:, Folder 63)
  - pp. 2317 - 2393, 1955 September 21 - 1956 July 25 (Box 4:, Folder 64)
  - pp. 2394 - 2463, 1956 October 17 - 1957 July 24 (Box 4:, Folder 65)
  - pp. 2464 - 2548, 1957 September 18 - 1958 July 16 (Box 4:, Folder 66)
  - pp. 2549 - 2586, 1958 September 17 - 1958 November 19 (Box 4:, Folder 67)
  - pp. 2582 - 2645, 1959 January 21 - 1959 July 15 (Box 4:, Folder 68)
  - pp. 2646 - 2688, 1959 September 16 - 1959 November 18 (Box 4:, Folder 69)
  - Budget Materials, 1958-1959 (Box 4:, Folder 70)
  - pp. 2689 - 2788, 1960 January 13 - 1960 July 20 (Box 4:, Folder 71)
  - pp. 2789 - 2829, 1960 September 21 - 1960 November 9 (Box 5:, Folder 72)
  - pp. 2830 - 2915, 1961 January 18 - 1961 August 16 (Box 5:, Folder 73)
  - pp. 2916 - 2968, 1961 September 27 - 1961 December 7 (Box 5:, Folder 74)
  - pp. 2969 - 3054, 1962 January 17 - 1962 August 7 (Box 5:, Folder 75)
  - pp. 3055 - 3115, 1962 September 17 - 1962 December 19 (Box 5:, Folder 76)
  - pp. 3116 - 3189, 1963 January 16 - 1963 July 17 (Box 5:, Folder 77)
  - Financial Aid Policies Committee Report, 1963 January 24 (Box 5:, Folder 78)
  - pp. 3190 - 3247, 1963 September 18 - 1963 December 18 (Box 5:, Folder 79)
  - pp. 3248 - 3322, 1964 January - 1964 August 12 (Box 5:, Folder 80)
  - pp. 3323 - 3370, 1964 September 16 - 1964 December 16 (Box 5:, Folder 81)
  - pp. 3371 - 3453, 1965 January 20 - 1965 July 21 (Box 5:, Folder 82)
  - pp. 3454 - 3520, 1965 September 15 - 1965 December 15 (Box 6:, Folder 83)
  - pp. 3251 - 3573, 1966 January 19 - 1966 April 20 (Box 6:, Folder 84)
  - pp. 3574 - 3619, 1966 May 18 - 1966 July 20 (Box 6:, Folder 85)
  - pp. 3620 - 3682, 1966 September 21 - 1966 December 21 (Box 6:, Folder 86)
  - pp. 3683 - 3772, 1967 January 18 - 1967 July 19 (Box 6:, Folder 87)
  - pp. 3774 - 3853, 1967 September 20 - 1967 December 20 (Box 6:, Folder 88)
  - pp. 3854 - 3918, 1968 January 17 - 1968 May 15 (Box 6:, Folder 89)
  - pp. 3919 - 3964, 1968 June 19 - 1968 July 17 (Box 6:, Folder 90)
  - pp. 3965 - 4046, 1968 September 18 - 1968 December 18 (Box 6:, Folder 91)
  - pp. 4047 - 4067, 1969 January 15 - 1969 January 25 (Box 6:, Folder 92)
  - pp. 4068 - 4114, 1969 February 19 - 1969 April 16 (Box 6:, Folder 93)
  - pp. 4115 - 4172, 1969 May 21 - 1969 July 16 (Box 6:, Folder 94)
  - pp. 4173 - 4215, 1969 September 17 - 1969 October 12 (Box 6:, Folder 95)
  - pp. 4216 - 4270, 1969 November 19 - 1969 December 6 (Box 6:, Folder 96)
  - pp. 4271 - 4332, 1970 January 21 - 1970 April 15 (Box 7:, Folder 97)
  - pp. 4333 - 4376, 1970 May 9 - 1970 June 17 (Box 7:, Folder 98)
  - pp. 4376 - 4459, 1970 July 15 - 1970 September 16 (Box 7:, Folder 99)
  - pp. 4460 - 4516, 1970 October 21 - 1970 December 16 (Box 7:, Folder 100)
  - pp. 4517 - 4533, 1971 January 21 (Box 7:, Folder 101)
  - pp. 4534 - 4549, 1971 February 17 (Box 7:, Folder 102)
  - pp. 4550 - 4564, 1971 March 17 (Box 7:, Folder 103)
  - pp. 4565 - 4581, 1971 April 21 (Box 7:, Folder 104)
  - pp. 4582 - 4597, 1971 May 19 (Box 7:, Folder 105)
  - pp. 4598 - 4617, 1971 June 16 (Box 7:, Folder 106)
  - pp. 4618 - 4643, 1971 July 21 (Box 7:, Folder 107)
  - pp. 4644 - 4655, 1971 August 18 (Box 7:, Folder 108)
  - pp. 4656 - 4693, 1971 September 15 (Box 7:, Folder 109)
  - pp. 4694 - 4718, 1971 October 20 (Box 7:, Folder 110)
  - pp. 4719 - 4739, 1971 November 17 (Box 8:, Folder 111)
  - pp. 4740 - 4757, 1971 December 15 (Box 8:, Folder 112)
  - pp. 4758 - 4781, 1972 January 19 (Box 8:, Folder 113)
  - pp. 4782 - 4816, 1972 February 16 (Box 8:, Folder 114)
  - pp. 4817 - 44843, 1972 March 15 (Box 8:, Folder 115)
  - pp. 4843 - 4859, 1972 April 19 (Box 8:, Folder 116)
  - pp. 4860 - 4878, 1972 May 17 (Box 8:, Folder 117)
  - pp. 4879 - 4901, 1972 June 21 (Box 8:, Folder 118)
  - pp. 4902 - 4933, 1972 July 19 (Box 8:, Folder 119)
  - pp. 4934 - 4951, 1972 August 16 (Box 8:, Folder 120)
  - pp. 4952 - 5001, 1972 September 15 - 1972 September 16 (Box 8:, Folder 121)
  - pp. 5002 - 5027, 1972 October 18 (Box 8:, Folder 122)
  - pp. 5028 - 5256, 1972 November 15 (Box 8:, Folder 123)
    - Attachments (Box 8:, Folder 124)
  - pp. 5057 - 5076, 1972 December 15 (Box 9:, Folder 125)
    - Attachments (Box 9:, Folder 126)
  - pp. 5077 - 5097, 1973 January (Box 9:, Folder 127)
    - Attachments (Box 9:, Folder 128)
  - pp. 5098 - 5138, 1973 February 8 - 1973 February 21 (Box 9:, Folder 129)
  - pp. 5139 - 5161, 1973 March 2 (Box 9:, Folder 130)
  - pp. 5162 - 5182, 1973 April 18 (Box 9:, Folder 131)
    - Attachments (Box 9:, Folder 132)
  - pp. 5183 - 5202, 1973 May 16 (Box 9:, Folder 133)
  - pp. 5203 - 5231, 1973 June 20 (Box 9:, Folder 134)
    - Attachments (Box 9:, Folder 135 - 136)
  - pp. 5232 - 5260, 1973 July 25 (Box 10:, Folder 137)
  - pp. 5261 - 5309, 1973 September 14 (Box 10:, Folder 138)
    - Attachments (Box 10:, Folder 139 - 140)
  - pp. 5310 - 5339, 1973 October 12 (Box 10:, Folder 141)
    - Attachments (Box 10:, Folder 142)
  - pp. 5340 - 5366, 1973 November 9 (Box 10:, Folder 143)
    - Attachments (Box 10:, Folder 144 - 145)
  - pp. 5367 - 5391, 1973 December 14 (Box 10:, Folder 146)
    - Attachments (Box 10:, Folder 147)
  - pp. 5392 - 5417, 1974 January 11 (Box 10:, Folder 148)
    - Attachments (Box 10:, Folder 149)
  - pp. 5418 - 5444, 1974 February 8 (Box 11:, Folder 150)
    - Attachments (Box 11:, Folder 151)
  - pp. 5445 - 5480, 1974 March 15 (Box 11:, Folder 152)
    - Attachments (Box 11:, Folder 153 - 154)
  - pp. 5481 - 5508, 1974 April 19 (Box 11:, Folder 155)
    - Attachments (Box 11:, Folder 156)
  - pp. 5509 - 5523, 1974 May 10 (Box 11:, Folder 157)
    - Attachments (Box 11:, Folder 158)
  - pp. 5524 - 5551, 1974 June 14 (Box 12:, Folder 159)
    - Attachments (Box 12:, Folder 160)
  - pp. 5552 - 5582, 1974 July 12 (Box 12:, Folder 161)
    - Attachments (Box 12:, Folder 162)
  - pp. 5583 - 5626, 1974 August 9 (Box 12:, Folder 163)
    - Attachments (Box 12:, Folder 164 - 166)
  - pp. 5627 - 5668, 1974 September 13 (Box 13:, Folder 167)
    - Attachments (Box 13:, Folder 168 - 169)
  - pp. 5669 - 5710, 1974 October 11 (Box 13:, Folder 170)
    - Attachments (Box 13:, Folder 171 - 172)
  - pp. 5711 - 5747, 1974 November 8 (Box 13:, Folder 173)
    - Attachments (Box 13:, Folder 174 - 175)
  - pp. 5748 - 5791, 1974 December 13 (Box 13:, Folder 176)
    - Attachments (Box 14:, Folder 177 - 178)
  - pp. 5792 - 5817, 1975 January 10 (Box 14:, Folder 179)
    - Attachments (Box 14:, Folder 180 - 181)
  - pp. 5818 - 5832, 1975 February 14 (Box 14:, Folder 182)
  - pp. 5833 - 5840, 1975 February 14 (Box 14:, Folder 183)
    - Attachments (Box 14:, Folder 184 - 185)
  - pp. 5840 - 5862, 1975 March 14 (Box 15:, Folder 186)
    - Attachments (Box 15:, Folder 187)
  - pp. 5863 - 5877, 1975 April 11 (Box 15:, Folder 188)
    - Attachments (Box 15:, Folder 189 - 190)
  - pp. 5878 - 5890, 1975 May 9 (Box 15:, Folder 191)
    - Attachments (Box 15:, Folder 192 - 193)
  - pp. 5891 - 5905, 1975 June 13 (Box 15:, Folder 194)
    - Attachments (Box 15:, Folder 195 - 196)
  - pp. 5906 - 5927, 1975 July 11 (Box 16:, Folder 197)
    - Attachments (Box 16:, Folder 198 - 199)
  - pp. 5927 - 5956, 1975 September 12 (Box 16:, Folder 200)
    - Attachments (Box 16:, Folder 201 - 203)
  - pp. 5957 - 5973, 1975 October 10 (Box 17:, Folder 204)
    - Attachments (Box 17:, Folder 205 - 206)
  - pp. 5974 - 5991, 1975 November 14 (Box 17:, Folder 207)
    - Attachments (Box 17:, Folder 208 - 209)
  - pp. 5992 - 6008, 1975 December 12 (Box 17:, Folder 210)
    - Attachments (Box 17:, Folder 211 - 212)
  - pp. 6009 - 6029, 1976 January 9 (Box 17:, Folder 213)
    - Attachments (Box 17:, Folder 214 - 215)
  - pp. 6030 - 6050, 1976 February 13 (Box 18:, Folder 216)
    - Attachments (Box 18:, Folder 217 - 218)
  - pp. 6051 - 6082, 1976 March 12 (Box 18:, Folder 219)
    - Attachments (Box 18:, Folder 220 - 221)
  - pp. 6085 - 6098, 1976 April 9 (Box 18:, Folder 222)
    - Attachments (Box 18:, Folder 223 - 224)
  - pp. 6099 - 6115, 1976 May 14 (Box 18:, Folder 225)
    - Attachments (Box 18:, Folder 226 - 227)
  - pp. 6116 - 6137, 1976 June 11 (Box 19:, Folder 228)
    - Attachments (Box 19:, Folder 229 - 230)
  - pp. 6138 - 6158, 1976 July 9 (Box 19:, Folder 231)
    - Attachments (Box 19:, Folder 232 - 233)
  - pp. 6159 - 6182, 1976 September 10 (Box 19:, Folder 234)
    - Attachments (Box 19:, Folder 235 - 236)
  - pp. 6183 - 6195, 1976 October 8 (Box 20:, Folder 237)
    - Attachments (Box 20:, Folder 238 - 239)
  - pp. 6196 - 6212, 1976 November 12 (Box 20:, Folder 240)
    - Attachments (Box 20:, Folder 241 - 242)
  - pp. 6213 - 6229, 1976 December 10 (Box 20:, Folder 243)
    - Attachments (Box 20:, Folder 244 - 245)
  - pp. 6230 - 6245, 1977 January 14 (Box 21:, Folder 246)
    - Attachments (Box 21:, Folder 247 - 248)
  - pp. 6246 - 6265, 1977 February 11 (Box 21:, Folder 249)
    - Attachments (Box 21:, Folder 250 - 251)
  - pp. 6266 - 6282, 1977 March 11 (Box 21:, Folder 252)
    - Attachments (Box 21:, Folder 253 - 254)
  - pp. 6283 - 6288, 1977 April 5 (Box 21:, Folder 255)
    - Attachments (Box 21:, Folder 256 - 257)
  - pp. 6289 - 6305, 1977 April 15 (Box 22:, Folder 258)
  - pp. 6306 - 6327, 1977 May 20 (Box 22:, Folder 259)
    - Attachments (Box 22:, Folder 260 - 261)
  - pp. 6333 - 6351, 1977 June 10 (Box 22:, Folder 262)
    - Attachments (Box 22:, Folder 263 - 264)
  - pp. 6352 - 6370, 1977 July 8 (Box 22:, Folder 265)
    - Attachments (Box 22:, Folder 266 - 267)
  - pp. 6371 - 6395, 1977 September 9 (Box 22:, Folder 268)
  - pp. 6396 - 6415, 1977 October 14 (Box 23:, Folder 269)
    - Attachments (Box 23:, Folder 270 - 271)
  - pp. 6416 - 6433, 1977 November 11 (Box 23:, Folder 272)
    - Attachments (Box 23:, Folder 273 - 274)
  - pp. 6434 - 6445, 1977 December 9 (Box 23:, Folder 275)
    - Attachments (Box 23:, Folder 276 - 277)
  - pp. 6446 - 6456, 1978 January 13 (Box 24:, Folder 278)
    - Attachments (Box 24:, Folder 279 - 280)
  - 1978 February 10 (Box 24:, Folder 281)
    - Attachments (Box 24:, Folder 282 - 283)
  - pp. 6457 - 6480, 1978 March 10 (Box 24:, Folder 284)
    - Attachments (Box 24:, Folder 285 - 286)
  - pp. 6481 - 6482, 1978 March 16 (Box 24:, Folder 287)
  - pp. 6483 - 6498, 1978 April 14 (Box 24:, Folder 288)
    - Attachments (Box 24:, Folder 289 - 290)
  - pp. 6499 - 6515, 1978 May 19 (Box 25:, Folder 291)
    - Attachments (Box 25:, Folder 292 - 293)
  - pp. 6516 - 6530, 1978 June 9 (Box 25:, Folder 294)
    - Attachments (Box 25:, Folder 295 - 296)
  - pp. 6531 - 6554, 1978 July 14 (Box 25:, Folder 297)
    - Attachments (Box 25:, Folder 298 - 299)
  - pp. 6555 - 6585, 1978 September 8 (Box 26:, Folder 300)
    - Attachments (Box 26:, Folder 301 - 302)
  - pp. 6586 - 6600, 1978 October 13 (Box 26:, Folder 303)
    - Attachments (Box 26:, Folder 304)
  - pp. 6601 - 6618, 1978 November 10 (Box 26:, Folder 305)
    - Attachments (Box 26:, Folder 306 - 307)
  - pp. 6619 - 6636, 1978 December 8 (Box 27:, Folder 308)
    - Attachments (Box 27:, Folder 309 - 310)
  - pp. 6637 - 6657, 1979 January 12 (Box 27:, Folder 311)
    - Attachments (Box 27:, Folder 312 - 313)
  - pp. 6658 - 6671, 1979 February 28 (Box 27:, Folder 314)
    - Attachments (Box 27:, Folder 315)
  - pp. 6672 - 6685, 1979 March 16 (Box 27:, Folder 316)
    - Attachments (Box 27:, Folder 317)
  - pp. 6686 - 6701, 1979 April 20 (Box 28:, Folder 318)
    - Attachments (Box 28:, Folder 319)
  - pp. 6702 - 6716, 1979 May 18 (Box 28:, Folder 320)
    - Attachments (Box 28:, Folder 321)
  - pp. 6717 - 6735, 1979 June 8 (Box 28:, Folder 322)
    - Attachments (Box 28:, Folder 323)
  - pp. 6736 - 6760, 1979 July 13 (Box 28:, Folder 324)
    - Attachments (Box 28:, Folder 325)
  - pp. 6761 - 6762, 1979 August 10 (Box 29:, Folder 326)
  - pp. 6763 - 6777, 1979 September 14 (Box 29:, Folder 327)
    - Attachments (Box 29:, Folder 328)
  - pp. 6778 - 6796, 1979 October 12 (Box 29:, Folder 329)
    - Attachments (Box 29:, Folder 330)
  - pp. 6797 - 6811, 1979 November 5 (Box 29:, Folder 331)
    - Attachments (Box 29:, Folder 332)
  - pp. 6812 - 6826, 1979 December 12 (Box 29:, Folder 333)
    - Attachments (Box 29:, Folder 334)
  - pp. 6827 - 6856, 1980 January 11 (Box 30:, Folder 335)
    - Attachments (Box 30:, Folder 336)
  - pp. 6857 - 6869, 1980 February 8 (Box 30:, Folder 337)
    - Attachments (Box 30:, Folder 338 - 339)
  - pp. 6870 - 6879, 1980 March 14 (Box 30:, Folder 340)
    - Attachments (Box 30:, Folder 341)
  - pp. 6880 - 6891, 1980 April 11 (Box 30:, Folder 342)
    - Attachments (Box 30:, Folder 343 - 344)
  - pp. 6892 - 6902, 1980 May 16 (Box 31:, Folder 345)
    - Attachments (Box 31:, Folder 346)
  - pp. 6903 - 6911, 1980 June 13 (Box 31:, Folder 347)
    - Attachments (Box 31:, Folder 348)
  - pp. 6912 - 6919, 1980 July 11 (Box 31:, Folder 349)
    - Attachments (Box 31:, Folder 350)
  - pp. 6920 - 6922, 1980 August 27 (Box 31:, Folder 351)
  - pp. 6923 - 6935, 1980 September 19 (Box 31:, Folder 352)
    - Attachments (Box 31:, Folder 353 - 354)
  - pp. 6936 - 6937, 1980 October 16 (Box 32:, Folder 355)
  - pp. 6938 - 6948, 1980 November 14 (Box 32:, Folder 356)
    - Attachments (Box 32:, Folder 357)
  - pp. 6956 - 6959, 1980 December 11 (Box 32:, Folder 358)
    - Attachments (Box 32:, Folder 359)
  - pp. 6958 - 6970, 1981 January 9 (Box 32:, Folder 360)
    - Attachments (Box 32:, Folder 361)
  - pp. 6971 - 6972, 1981 February 12 (Box 32:, Folder 362)
  - pp. 6973 - 6983, 1981 March 13 (Box 33:, Folder 363)
    - Attachments (Box 33:, Folder 364 - 366)
  - pp. 6984 - 6985, 1981 April 9 (Box 33:, Folder 367)
  - pp. 6986 - 6993, 1981 May 22 (Box 33:, Folder 368)
  - pp. 6994 - 6995, 1981 May 28 (Box 33:, Folder 369)
    - Attachments (Box 33:, Folder 370 - 372)
  - 1981 June 11 (Box 33:, Folder 373)
  - pp. 6997 - 7006, 1981 July 10 (Box 34:, Folder 374)
    - Attachments (Box 34:, Folder 375 - 376)
  - pp. 7007 - 7014, 1981 September 18 (Box 34:, Folder 377)
    - Attachments (Box 34:, Folder 378 - 379)